[{"answer": "I didn't forget.  I was up all night thinking about it and I concluded you're too special to look like everyone else.  Orange Red.  That's your color.  Few can carry it off.  Now please.  Help me find your brother", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Of course not.  Does he look lost to you?  BENNNNN!!", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Since our divorce my friend has seen a number of different women in three short years and without a lot of warning for the kids, he's now living with a woman half his age", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We're not discussing your age", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend's not half my age", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, we're not discussing my friend's age either", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Me too", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Fine.  But I wanted to take the kids to work with me on Wednesday so I'll take Wednesday, and you can pick up that Thursday, Friday after soccer, and Saturday before riding", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Mass hysteria", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm not upset.  Why would I be upset", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Seven of clubs.  Nobody's mad we just want to talk about it", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend, daddy and I will always be there. That's one time always is always.  You can call him after dinner but..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I just found out I have to go to that place to get a deposition.  I might not be back until Saturday", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " We have the kids this weekend, so..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What I meant and perhaps I didn't say it well was you have a great mom.  You don't need another one.  But when you're at this house", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "This is my house too", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Every Tuesday except the 3rd Tuesday of the month when it's switched to Friday except in April when she rides on Thursday.  It's not that hard.  Didn't you have a mother", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We don't have any coffee", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " No, that's your fault.  It's her fault for not watching over my precious son, as if it were her priority.  Which means, the most important job", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend, mommies work too.  They work very hard.  Mommy works harder as a mom than she did when she was working.  I just don't get paid", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend, mommies work too.  They work very hard.  Mommy works harder as a mom than she did when she was working.  I just don't get paid", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "People like my friend who only think about themselves often do make a lot of money", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh my God.  Are you serious", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I think so too..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Where's Rache?  It's , we get to be with ", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "She's  is your mother now", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Mrs. my friend...", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "How tall is your tree?  The really, really, , REALLY big..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why don't you say hello", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend pick up the phone", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend pick up the phone", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "That doesn't bother me", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That doesn't bother me", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You think this is funny", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You think this is funny", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No.  I think it's ugly", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "And you tell her.  What you're going to say", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " No, baby.  You're gonna use words", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You're lying", "docId": "stepmom.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You are lying, you never lost that kid for 4 , you could find him from a , there is no WAY", "qsentId": 40}]